It is now time to get some practice adding dummy variables to a linear model.
现在我们练习一下把虚拟变量添加到线性模型中
In this video we'll do this together.
在这个视频中我们共同完成
Then in the next concept you'll do this on your own.
然后在接下来的概念中你要独立完成
First let's load the necessary libraries and the data.
首先我们加载必要的库和数据
In order to create our dummy variables,
为了创建虚拟变量
Pandas has a useful method called Get dummies.
Pandas 提供了一种实用方法 叫做 get_dummy
A quick google search gets us to the documentation.
通过谷歌快速搜索可以得到这个文档
Let's see how this works.
让我们来看一下如何运用它
If we pass our categorical column to get dummies,
如果我们把分类列传递 得到虚拟变量
the output we get is just what you saw in
得到的输出是你在之前视频中见到的
the earlier video where each output column is one
每个输出列都是其中一个分类水平
of the categorical levels and the value of each column is either a one or a zero.
每列值要么是 1 要么是 0
So if we pass the neighborhood column,
如果传递街区一列
you'll see that we get back the A's,
你会发现得到 A
B's and C's where there's three B's here and
B 和 C 其中这里有三个 B
you can see there's three ones there and then there's an A.
发现这里有三个 1 然后这有一个 A
And so we see the one for the A and there's basically
所以我们看到这个 1 表示 A
zeroes otherwise for these other columns.
其他 0 表示其余这些列
Let's store this output A,
我们存储为输出结果 A
B and C. As you saw in the earlier quiz,
B C 正如你在之前练习所见
just using the categorical columns in our linear models didn't work.
只使用线性模型中的分类列无法起作用
Let's see if we have more success using
我们来看一下
these dummy variables and our linear regression model.
使用虚拟变量和线性回归模型能不能更成功
Here I've created the neighborhood.
这里我已经创建了街区
Let's do this again with the style.
然后采用相同方式创建风格
Your categorical variables will always come back in alphabetical order so,
分类变量总是以字母顺序呈现
whichever comes first alphabetically is
按照字母顺序首先出现的
the first one that will be returned as your column.
也会首先返回到列中
So before you saw that we couldn't pass
所以在你看到这个前 我们不能
these categorical variables straight into our linear regression models.
直接把这些虚拟变量传递到线性回归模型中
Let's try again using these dummy variables.
我们再次尝试使用这些虚拟变量
Remember, you will always want to drop one of the columns.
记住你总是要舍弃其中一列
The column you drop is called the baseline category here.
你舍弃的这列称为基准类别
Let's drop the Victorian column and just use these other two.
我们来舍弃维多利亚一列 只使用另外两列
So we're gonna drop this column and just use these two here.
这样我们舍弃这一列 使用这两列
And similarly we could create the baseline with A,
同样我们创建基准为 A B 和 C
B or C so we'll drop one of those when we add it to our linear model.
添加到线性模型时舍弃其中一个
To create a linear model that just uses the homes, we can do the following.
为了创建只使用房屋的线性模型 我们可以这样做
So we'll be predicting the price.
我们将要预测价格
And let's add an intercept.
增加一个截距
And then in our model,
然后是在模型中
I'll have the intercept.
我得到这个截距
So here you can see we have more success.
所以这里你看到我们成功几率更大
Here, we fit the model and then
这里我们拟合模型
finally we can look at the results with the summary command.
最终可以看到包含摘要指令的结果
Let's interpret a few of these coefficients.
我们来解释其中一些系数
So this has six zeros on the end of it.
结尾有六个 0
So 1 2 3,
所以 1 2 3
so it's like one million.
这个相当于 100 万
So the intercept means that if our home is a Victorian home,
这个截距表明如果房屋是维多利亚风格
we predict its price to be 1,046,000 dollars
预测价格为 1,046,000 美元
and lodge is predicted to be 741,000 less than a Victorian.
林间小屋的价格比维多利亚房屋低 741,000 美元
And similarly, a ranch is predicted to be 471,000 less than a Victorian.
同样 平房的价格比维多利亚房屋低 471,000 美元
So each of these is a comparison to
这些与基准类别形成对比
the baseline category and this is our prediction for the baseline.
可以得出对基准类别的估算